{"data":[{"question":"His wife died in ________ when he was only 24 years old.","a":"children","b":"childhood","c":"childbed","d":"childbirth","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Childbed: The condition of a woman in the process of giving birth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"________ policeman directing the traffic.","a":"Take care of","b":"Take track of","c":"Keep an eye on","d":"Pay attention to","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Pay attention to: when you carefully listen to, look at, or think about someone or something.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"The bomb ________ when he rang the bell.","a":"went over","b":"went on","c":"went out","d":"went off","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Go off: to explode or fire.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"No one really believed it when the news came through that the \"Titanic\" had ________ on her maiden voyage.","a":"gone over","b":"gone on","c":"gone down","d":"gone off","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Go down: if a ship goes down, it sinks.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Does this jacket ________ my trousers?","a":"go with","b":"go through with","c":"go ahead","d":"go off","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Go with: if colours, tastes, styles etc go with, they look, taste etc good together.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"He ________ about his new car all the time.","a":"goes over","b":"goes on","c":"goes out","d":"goes off","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Go on about: to talk too much.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you think you could ________ this work with me some time, Peter?","a":"go over","b":"go on","c":"go out","d":"go off","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Go over: to repeat something in order to explain it or make sure it is correct.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"We have permission to ________ with the plan.","a":"go ahead","b":"go over","c":"go on","d":"go off","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Go ahead: to start to do something, especially after planning it or asking permission to do it.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"I know you find the course boring, Pauline, but since you've started it, you might as well ________ it.","a":"go with","b":"go through with","c":"go ahead","d":"go off","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Go through with: to do something you had promised or planned to do, even though it causes problems or you are no longer sure you want to do it","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Take a map with you ________ you lose your way.","a":"in case","b":"so","c":"because","d":"although","answer":"1","explain":"\n- In case: as a way of being safe from something that might happen or might be true.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"}]}